Hi, in this lesson, you will learn how to install and set up Google Integrity on your computer.
We will walk through the entire process step by step so you can start using this powerful
AI code into right away.
Let's download the install request.
This open your browser and go to the official Google Integrity website and click download
button.
Right here, you can choose the version you have to download for your specific platform.
You use my course of Windows or Linux and click download.
After you go download, please follow the instructions to set up an application and set
open it.
And you go see this welcome screen and I will help you to set up the right way.
So if you are using past any code editor like VS code, Windows or for course or you can import
all the settings from it.
If not, just click start fresh but I will use import from Windows to your code.
I will also use a check mark to import team from the Windows to your code settings but
if you don't like to do it, just choose the team you'd like or leave the dark as default.
Then click next, so on this screen you see some configuration for agent agent is a AI assistant
which helped you to work with your tasks.
I recommend you to leave everything as easy and later on when you will better understand
all the settings how you come for to work with agent, you can configure it by yourself
in the settings.
So let's click next.
On this screen you can set up the guidance, you'd like to use a normal one from the VIM in
the shortcuts.
I recommend you leave everything as easy unless you know why you need to change it.
So let's click next and on this step you need to sign in to Google account.
This step is important because it links your AI usage to your Google account unless you
see all your settings across different devices, so this is a required step.
Okay, let's sign in, as you see I can click next to your mobile game.
I will sign in to my account, you can do it same for you and we will continue after I will
finish the sign in.
Okay, after you sign it in, you can, so you can accept the terms.
So please read them, nothing special, same as most of the codaditerous services, so adjust
you can read it.
I will click next and now I see my editor is set up, SSC onboarding installation extensions
is still ongoing, so after you've finished as the message is gone and so in the next video
you will go through this antigravity codaditer and I will explain how to use it, so see you
in the next lesson.